

<u>Lara Banat</u>

Mua'mmar Bin Alharith St, Amman, Jordan • +962795246792 •Larabelal07@gmail.com

SUMMARY

With around 5 years of experience in the financial field, I possess comprehensive knowledge of market dynamics, trading strategies, and banking transfers (SWIFT). My strong background in exchange software's, currency exchange, and rates in global prices screen sets me apart in the industry. I have proven skills in Creativity, Persuasion, Leadership, and Decision Making. My professional communication skills include fluency in English and Arabic. I hold a bachelor's degree in financial and banking science with a very good rate. Additionally, my computer skills include MS Office, internet, and email. I offer a comprehensive network of money transfer options, making me a valuable asset in the financial sector.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Head Teller - Supervisor

Swiss Exchange, Amman, Jordan

FEB 2023-Present

- Manage and oversee the daily operations of the teller line.
- Train and develop new tellers.
- Resolve customer issues and complaints.
- Balance cash drawers and reconcile accounts.
- Offering a comprehensive network of money transfer options for seamless transactions.
- Prepare and submit reports and comply with all regulatory requirements.
- Handle transactions involving the buying and selling of foreign currency.
- Efficiently manage all outgoing and incoming transfers

Teller and customer services officer

AUG 2022-FEB 2023

Al-Alami Exchange, Amman, Jordan

- Handle customer transactions accurately and efficiently.
- Verify customer identification and ensure that all transactions comply with central bank policies and procedures.
- Provide excellent customer service.
- Exchanging foreign currency, including buying and selling foreign currency and verifying the authenticity of foreign currency notes
- Checking customer IDs and verifying signatures.
- Following anti-money laundering (AML) procedures.
- Complying with Know Your Customer (KYC) regulations.
- Partnering with a wide range of money transfer services for convenient transactions.

Lara Banat Page 2 of 2

Teller and customer service

FEB 2019-MAY 2022

Al-Sayyed Exchange, Amman, Jordan

- Efficiently manage customer transactions, including deposits, withdrawals, cash advances.
- Handle all aspects of foreign currency exchange, including buying, selling, and verifying authenticity.
- Handle foreign currency transactions with expertise, verifying authenticity and maintaining accurate exchange rates.
- Verify customer identities, signatures, and KYC compliance to protect against fraud and maintain financial integrity.
- Follow AML procedures to prevent money laundering.
- Adhere to central bank regulations and procedures to ensure compliance and safeguard customer funds.
- Partnering with a wide range of money transfer services for convenient transactions.

EDUCATION

Bachelor Degree in Financial and Banking Science

2019

Al Balqa' Applied University/ Faculty of Engineering

Rate: Very Good

GPA: 3.37

SKILLS

- Attention to detail and accuracy
- Ability to process transactions accurately and efficiently
- Proficiency in Microsoft Office Suite
- Experience with financial software applications
- Excellent time management skills
- Strong problem-solving skills
- Ability to work under pressure
- Productive team player
- Demonstrate unwavering honesty and ethical behavior in all professional interactions.